[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "CC", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "TO", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "But did it surprise you that in that moment, even at his young age, that he was showing such enterprising courage?", "question_tokens": ["But", "did", "it", "surprise", "you", "that", "in", "that", "moment", ",", "even", "at", "his", "young", "age", ",", "that", "he", "was", "showing", "such", "enterprising", "courage", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "That's what's said happened and that's what's going around, that the kids made or were attempting to make a run or to escape.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "what", "'s", "said", "happened", "and", "that", "'s", "what", "'s", "going", "around", ",", "that", "the", "kids", "made", "or", "were", "attempting", "to", "make", "a", "run", "or", "to", "escape", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 87, "question": "What is the answer?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "answer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 88, "answer": "Well, first of all, this is not as rare as people might think.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "this", "is", "not", "as", "rare", "as", "people", "might", "think", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["today"]}, "docId": "121219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "And is the president right to identify the solution to at least trying to deal with this as being the -- banning these type of assault weapons and the high-capacity magazine clips and also, as Mayor Booker says here, trying to register the ownership of guns in a more sensible manner?", "question_tokens": ["And", "is", "the", "president", "right", "to", "identify", "the", "solution", "to", "at", "least", "trying", "to", "deal", "with", "this", "as", "being", "the", "--", "banning", "these", "type", "of", "assault", "weapons", "and", "the", "high-capacity", "magazine", "clips", "and", "also", ",", "as", "Mayor", "Booker", "says", "here", ",", "trying", "to", "register", "the", "ownership", "of", "guns", "in", "a", "more", "sensible", "manner", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "IN", "JJS", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "VBG", "DT", ":", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "RB", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "I think the president recognized today in a very appropriate statement that we have to take a look at a variety of risk factors that have created this epidemic, this carnage.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "president", "recognized", "today", "in", "a", "very", "appropriate", "statement", "that", "we", "have", "to", "take", "a", "look", "at", "a", "variety", "of", "risk", "factors", "that", "have", "created", "this", "epidemic", ",", "this", "carnage", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Mayor Booker"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Michigan Coalition for Responsible"]}, "docId": "121219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", ":", "JJ", "RP", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 186, "question": "What is your reaction?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "reaction", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 187, "answer": "My reaction is I -- first off, on behalf of the entire Michigan Coalition for Responsible Gun Owners, I want to express sincere sympathy to those who have lost loved ones.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "reaction", "is", "I", "--", "first", "off", ",", "on", "behalf", "of", "the", "entire", "Michigan", "Coalition", "for", "Responsible", "Gun", "Owners", ",", "I", "want", "to", "express", "sincere", "sympathy", "to", "those", "who", "have", "lost", "loved", "ones", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 201, "question": "As Christiane says, these belong -- not belong but they are found on the battlefields of Sarajevo, of Syria?", "question_tokens": ["As", "Christiane", "says", ",", "these", "belong", "--", "not", "belong", "but", "they", "are", "found", "on", "the", "battlefields", "of", "Sarajevo", ",", "of", "Syria", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "VBZ", ",", "DT", "JJ", ":", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 202, "answer": "Well, my thinking on this is they are out there.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "my", "thinking", "on", "this", "is", "they", "are", "out", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Sarajevo", "Syria"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Dunblane"]}, "docId": "121219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "OK, and what happened after '97 to the murder rate in England?", "question_tokens": ["OK", ",", "and", "what", "happened", "after", "'97", "to", "the", "murder", "rate", "in", "England", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "CC", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "-NONE-", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "After Dunblane, they put in these bans.", "answer_tokens": ["After", "Dunblane", ",", "they", "put", "in", "these", "bans", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["England"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 323, "question": "What is going to change this culture?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "going", "to", "change", "this", "culture", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 324, "answer": "Piers, this is what's going to change it.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "this", "is", "what", "'s", "going", "to", "change", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "RB", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "What is your belief about the claim that many people that, that if the teachers had been armed at Sandy Hook, that they could have averted the disaster, and that civilians should be armed for that reason, to protect themselves from mass killings like this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "belief", "about", "the", "claim", "that", "many", "people", "that", ",", "that", "if", "the", "teachers", "had", "been", "armed", "at", "Sandy", "Hook", ",", "that", "they", "could", "have", "averted", "the", "disaster", ",", "and", "that", "civilians", "should", "be", "armed", "for", "that", "reason", ",", "to", "protect", "themselves", "from", "mass", "killings", "like", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", ",", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "Let me just very quickly say, I'm very sorry to all the parents who lost their children and to the other people who lost the adults in this massacre.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "me", "just", "very", "quickly", "say", ",", "I", "'m", "very", "sorry", "to", "all", "the", "parents", "who", "lost", "their", "children", "and", "to", "the", "other", "people", "who", "lost", "the", "adults", "in", "this", "massacre", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Sandy Hook"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "But as she said, people should be trained for these use, right?", "question_tokens": ["But", "as", "she", "said", ",", "people", "should", "be", "trained", "for", "these", "use", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "Well, of course.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 472, "question": "What law do you propose that would have stopped this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "law", "do", "you", "propose", "that", "would", "have", "stopped", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 473, "answer": "Here's what I think: you have to try.", "answer_tokens": ["Here", "'s", "what", "I", "think", ":", "you", "have", "to", "try", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "Why don't you tell me, Mr. Lott?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "n't", "you", "tell", "me", ",", "Mr.", "Lott", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "OK.", "answer_tokens": ["OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Lott"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 490, "question": "How many bullets can it fire in a second?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "bullets", "can", "it", "fire", "in", "a", "second", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 491, "answer": "There's a reason --", "answer_tokens": ["There", "'s", "a", "reason", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 500, "question": "How many bullets does the AR 15 fire a second?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "bullets", "does", "the", "AR", "15", "fire", "a", "second", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "CD", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 501, "answer": "The point --", "answer_tokens": ["The", "point", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 505, "question": "Do you want to answer or not?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "want", "to", "answer", "or", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 506, "answer": "I'm going to answer your first question.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "going", "to", "answer", "your", "first", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", ":"], "qSentId": 514, "question": "How many bullets does it fire a second?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "bullets", "does", "it", "fire", "a", "second", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 515, "answer": "The point is --", "answer_tokens": ["The", "point", "is", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "Can you answer the question or not?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "answer", "the", "question", "or", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJR", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "You will lose lives.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "will", "lose", "lives", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 525, "question": "Do you know?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 526, "answer": "I think your estimate is high.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "your", "estimate", "is", "high", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 549, "question": "If you were trying to debate this in a more rational way than I appear capable of, what would you do?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "were", "trying", "to", "debate", "this", "in", "a", "more", "rational", "way", "than", "I", "appear", "capable", "of", ",", "what", "would", "you", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 550, "answer": "But I understand your passion, having stood on too many street corners, seen too many bodies, seen the kind of weapons we're pulling of the streets.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "I", "understand", "your", "passion", ",", "having", "stood", "on", "too", "many", "street", "corners", ",", "seen", "too", "many", "bodies", ",", "seen", "the", "kind", "of", "weapons", "we", "'re", "pulling", "of", "the", "streets", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 580, "question": "What do you think of this debate?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "this", "debate", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 581, "answer": "There are three points that I think need to be raised.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "are", "three", "points", "that", "I", "think", "need", "to", "be", "raised", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 589, "question": "Do you want to see these assault rifles just gone?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "want", "to", "see", "these", "assault", "rifles", "just", "gone", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 590, "answer": "You know, I think getting rid of the assault weapons, you know, it is not a perfect bill, but we will never be able to legislate against evil.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "think", "getting", "rid", "of", "the", "assault", "weapons", ",", "you", "know", ",", "it", "is", "not", "a", "perfect", "bill", ",", "but", "we", "will", "never", "be", "able", "to", "legislate", "against", "evil", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 612, "question": "Are you aghast that it isn't a national thing?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "aghast", "that", "it", "is", "n't", "a", "national", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 613, "answer": "I am.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 628, "question": "What is your view?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "view", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 629, "answer": "I absolutely believe in banning those weapons.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "absolutely", "believe", "in", "banning", "those", "weapons", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "NN", ",", "CC", "NNP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 639, "question": "What is your view?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "view", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 640, "answer": "My view is that all military style weapons should be banned, period, and Background checks for all.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "view", "is", "that", "all", "military", "style", "weapons", "should", "be", "banned", ",", "period", ",", "and", "Background", "checks", "for", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]